

## **Evan Hahn**

**Phone number:** (707) 695-0848

Email address: evanhahn3@gmail.com

Portfolio: https://evan-j-hahn.github.io/myportfolio/

**GitHub:** https://github.com/Evan-J-Hahn

### Objective

I am an ambitious, self-taught Web Developer that is ready to turn a passion into a career. With over 5 years of self-driven coursework and projects, I have experience prototyping internal tools, creating attractive user interfaces, scalable databases, as well as testing and debugging.

### Experience

05/2019 – 03/2020 Tangent, Oregon

### Senior Lab Director Vero Naturals

- Managed and trained the production team in a fast-paced start up environment
- Created and implemented production and testing protocols that met USDA FSIS guidelines
- Designed and maintained Excel spreadsheets to track production and test data
- Utilized reports to optimize current process and procedures
- Collaborated with third-party state and federally accredited testing labs to achieve and maintain industry standard product qualities

05/2017 – 03/2019 Keizer, Oregon

### Farm Manager EVO-AG Solutions LLC

- Designed and implemented large scale irrigation systems for optimizing crop production and water consumption efficiency
- Collaborated with the marketing and sales team to create a client network which resulted in a 15% increase in quarterly sales revenue
- Supervised and trained multiple teams of 20+ employees that oversaw daily field maintenance and crop quality control

01/2012 – 02/2014 San Rafael, California

### Sales Marketing Assistant Marin Mortgage Group

- Maintained and organized databases responsible for tracking current and potential sales leads
- Used data-driven model to optimize the company's focused audience
- Assisted in the creation, design and finalization of marketing materials including monthly newsletters and urgent rate changes through physical and digital mediums

#### Education

01/2014 – 12/2016 Santa Rosa, California

# Completed Computer Science Course Work Santa Rosa Junior College

- CS10 Introduction to Programming C++
- CS11 Data Structures & Algorithms C++
- CS81.21 Introduction to Unix
- CS12 Assembly Language Programming
- CS50A Web Development 1
- CS50B Web Development 2

#### Education

03/2020 – 09/2020 Online

### **Udemy**

- The Complete Node.js Developer Course
- The Complete React Developer Course (Hooks and Redux)
- The Modern GraphQL Bootcamp (with Node.js and Apollo)
- The Complete React Developer in 2020 (with React, Hooks and GraphQL)
- Bootstrap 4 From Scratch

Skills —	
JavaScript	Node.js
HTML 5	React.js
CSS 3	Redux
Sass	Express
C++	PostgreSQL
MongoDB	Firebase

#### **Certificates**

08/2020

# Responsive Web Design Certification FreeCodeCamp

- HTML5
- CSS 3
- Applied Visual Design
- Applied Accessibility
- Responsive Web Design Principles
- CSS Flexbox
- CSS Grid

09/2020

# Front End Libraries Certification FreeCodeCamp

- Bootstrap
- jQuery
- Sass
- React
- Redux

10/2020

# Data Visualiztion Certification FreeCodeCamp

- Data Visualization with D3
- JSON API's
- Ajax